Come on, give the Lord a shout in here!
Hallelujah - as we continue to lift up the name of Jesus!
Hallelujah You have won the victory
Lift up your voice and say:
Hallelujah You have won it all for me
Death could not hold You down
You are the risen King
Seated in Majesty
Death could not hold You down
You are the risen King
Seated in Majesty
Let me say it like this:
Death could not hold You down
The grave could not contain You
Because You have risen
Now I have a reason
A reason to praise You
And live my life for You
Precious Redeemer
You reign forever
Death could not hold You down
The grave could not contain You
Because You have risen
We all have a reason
A reason to praise Your name
And live my life for You
Precious Redeemer
You reign forever
Death could not hold You down
You are the risen King
Seated in majesty
We love You
You are the risen King
Good Morning, Church!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you.
Happy New Year!
I know you are feeling the atmosphere by faith.
Thank you. Hallelujah.
Viewers all over the world, Happy New Year!
By faith, you have been ushered to the New Year!
Hallelujah.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
I know the thinking of every Christian is how to remain focused.
Our Christian life demands for that.
I say, "Remain focused".
No matter what happens, no matter what comes, your focus should not be broken.
Your focus should not be what?
Broken.
Hallelujah!
Let us just reflect about the year we are waiting for, the outgoing and incoming year.
To many others, the New Year is one with a new possession -
a new house, cars, friends, children, a new job, relations.
Just think about that.
To many others, they think they are fulfilled when they have all these.
To them, it is a New Year indeed.
A New Year is a gift from God - a part of divine nature of God.
If the New Year is a part of the divine nature of God,
in the New Year, therefore, you are called to God's kind of lifestyle - His divine essence,
not in terms of unfaithfulness, injustice and corruption
but of steadfastness, faithfulness and love.
I want to remind you the promise of God, the New Morning Water is out for the year.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Now, it is time for the work of faith. It takes faith to receive it.
It's out to fight the hardship and demon that cause you to lose control and commit shameful acts.
It's out to fight it!
That is it.
I will have a great relief this new year because of this.
A great relief.
Because when you have it, you only come and gives thanks to God.
Ok. This is it.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Remember, God is the reason for the year.
Tell your neighbour.
Nothing of God can be possible without our heart being pure.
That is why you keep trying and trying by error; it is not possible.
God is the reason for the year.
Nothing of God can be possible unless our heart is pure.
Christ tells us in Matthew 5:8, 'Blessed are the pure in heart; they shall see God in the year'.
That is why you keep trying and trying, writing application, doing this and that, praying
because your heart is not pure - grudges, pain of the past, holding offence.
Forgive us as we forgive those who sin against us - this is our confession but we fail to follow this.
Nothing of God can be possible unless our heart is pure.
You have to dedicate your heart to the Word of God.
The Word of God is not to memorise but mediate on it day and night.
I mean, you have to abide in the Word.
Let the Word of God abide in you and you abide in it.
Look at my Faith Bracelet.
This is why we came out with this.
My own is here.
That is why we came out with this - to help you.
As you are sitting now, you are supposed to fire on.
Take more of me, give me more of You, oh Lord Jesus.
This is what we mean by meditating on it day and night.
All those days in the house, you sit watching your television,
watching all sorts of programmes.
As you are watching your programme, fire on.
It is not every time you can go to your altar on your knees and pray before going to sleep.
Sometimes, you get so tired.
You just go on your bed, let it be in your hand, 'Take more of me, give me more of You'
and you sleep off.
Inside the plane, inside the vehicle.
But people seem to turn it to fashion now.
When they are going, they ask, "Which colour?"
"Blue, red, yellow..."
Well done.
Nothing of God can be possible unless your heart is pure.
Pure means free spirit.
But your heart is not free.
You think of affliction, your problem, this and that,
how to get this, how to celebrate the new year.
What is that?
You need a free spirit to contact the Spirit of God.
Nothing of God can be possible unless your heart is free.
Dedicate your heart to the Word of God.
This will help you to dedicate it.
By the time you continue to meditate on it, it will become an integral part of your being.
'Take more of me, give me more of You.'
You have to dedicate your heart to the Word of God.
Meditate on it day and night.
Let the Word abide in you and you in it.
To have a new beginning which we call New Year, the Word of God must dominate your heart.
It's not just by reading but by meditation.
Meditation brings revelation.
Then, you can stop looking and thinking about where you are coming from.
We are coming from unrighteousness which boasts in itself.
When we have breakthrough, we say, "Hey, it's by our hard work!"
But when failure comes, you begin to look for a scapegoat.
"Why does God not answer me? I attend church regularly."
But when you are okay, you never...
This coming year - I'm supposed to bring the revelation, what you should expect next year.
I compiled everything.
I was just looking at it. Many of those things are things you already know about
because the signs we are seeing now cannot be overcome in just one year.
This coming year is a year you must be ready to fight the battle to survive.
Think of your survival.
It's a year your children need to sit at your feet and learn from you.
Share your experience with them - it's a parable.
I will bring the prophecies to you.
But I don't know...
Before I give them to you, take your time to go through what I said last year.
Go and read more about what I said last year.
Just look at what I said last year
so that when you receive this, you will not be ignorant.
We are in a warfare where the serious-minded will be victorious.
When you dedicate your heart to the Word of God,
you have that ability from God to stop looking or thinking about where you are coming from
and start looking at where you are going.
That is the ability from God.
It's not possible for anyone to say, "No, I forget about the past", without God
because it's only that information satan has about you - your past.
It appears that it is the only information satan has - your past.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you.
Viewers, your position is known to God.
Be set free, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Every unfavourable situation you have been in, right from your journey -
today is a closing day for the year.
Your unfavourable situation is closed, in the name of Jesus!
Be closed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Arise, in the name of Jesus!
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
In Jesus Christ's name!
Your career, rise and shine!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Say, My career, rise and shine!
It is time to rise and shine, in Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name